Katsiaryna Symanovich OA Engineer

QA Engineer Belarus, Minsk





Katsiaryna_Symanovich



@katsiaryna-symanovich

symanovichkatsiaryna@gmail.com

Summary

Solution-oriented, motivated specialist with extensive technical skills and education. Aimed at highly effective teamwork using excellent communication skills.

Languages

English: Pre-Intermediate – Intermediate

I'm taking the English courses and constantly learning by myself.

Additional Education (certificates)

QA Engineer

Author's course by Vadim Ksendzov <u>link</u> 07/2021 – 10/2021

"Tester course from scratch" by Artsiom Rusau on youtube 07/2021

uTest Academy

Education

Systems engineer

Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics

2017 (Bachelor degree)

Technician-programmer

Minsk Radioengineering College 2007 (Associate degree)

Work Experience

Junior QA Engineer (Practice)

Author's course by Vadim Ksendzov (capital.com) 07/2021-present

During the course were applied:

Manual testing, Functional testing, API testing (Postman), Load testing (Jmeter), Localization testing of mobile apps.

Crowdtesting

Applause 2020-2021

Writing <u>bug reports</u>, running test cases, collecting logs, capturing video of the device screen, screenshots, the AI Video Collection on the projects: <u>shop.lululemon.com</u>, <u>mylifebox.com</u>, <u>claires.com</u>, Artificial Intelligence system.

Technician-programmer

BA Konkurs

2010-present

Master of industrial training of a computer operator

Vocational college 2007-2009

Skills

- Check Lists <u>link1</u>, <u>link2</u>
- Bug Reports <u>link</u>
- **SQL** <u>link</u>
- Postman link
- sending requests (GET, POST, PUT, DELETE), creating an environment, launching a collection;
- writing autotests: checking the answer, checking the json structure, transferring numbers to the environment, checking the coefficients, comparing numbers, checking the correctness of the received values
 - Git, GitHub <u>link</u>

Working with local and remote repositories (creating / deleting a repository, files, branches; adding files to Git, creating commits, merging to the main branch, connecting an SSH key).

• LINUX commands - <u>link</u>

cd, ls, pwd, mkdir, touch, find, rm, cat, rmdir, mv, tail, grep, less, date, sudo, curl, chmod, head

• Charles – <u>link</u>, Fiddler - <u>link</u>

Installing a certificate, configuring a proxy server, intercepting and analyzing traffic.

JavaScript (basics)

For writing tests in Postman to check the response from the server.

Android Studio

Run apps on the Android Emulator and a real device.

• ADB

Connecting the device via wi-fi, install / uninstall application, capturing log files, taking screenshots.

- DevTools (Google Chrome)
- **JMeter** link

Basic knowledges of Load testing, Spike.

• HTML